't know why anyone would miss an episode of
Glee,
Quinn's parents found out she's pregnant
I needed my mom.
MERCEDES: So it's decided.
You move in with me.
Jessie dropped Rachel and McKinley
And that's what you missed on Glee.
Hey, buddy, see you on Saturday.
Wait. What?
At Regionals. Didn't you hear?
I'm one of the judges.
You cannot allow this to happen!
It's out of my hands, William.
I have no control over what
Let me break it down for you, Will.
It's been decided that this year's Regionals
And I'm a celebrity
Now I realize my cultural
I'm a legend. It's happened.
Do you have any idea how hard my kids have been working, Sue?
I have to be honest, Will.
I'm having a really difficult time hearing
I keep expecting racist
Principal Figgins, I am begging you.
Do not let her do this to those kids.
William, I resent the implication
You leaked our set list at Sectionals, Sue.
I have no memory of that.
I will not let you do this.
We have worked ourselves to the bone to get where we are.
I'm sorry, Will, but our arrangement stands.
You must win or place at Regionals,
If I were you, I would spend
Good luck with that, Will.
Sync By YesCool WwW.MY-SUBS.com
I can't do this.
Yes, you can.
Have another wine cooler.
I'm president of the Celibacy Club.
I took a vow.
So did Santana and Brittany, and I did them.
What about Finn?
He's your best friend.
Come on. We're in high school.
You think either one of us is going to give a damn
Life's just a bunch of experiences, you know?
You don't get a medal at the finish line for being good.
You just get dead.
Okay, but you can't tell anybody.
I can't lose my rep.
Our secret, baby.
What about protection?
I got it, trust me.
This isn't just another hookup for me.
Tell me one more time.
You're not fat.
WILL: Quinn?
Quinn?
Are you all right?
It's been a long year.
Yeah.
Oh, you need some help with those plates?
I'm not due for a month.
Think I can handle a stack of plates.
Right. I'm...
Yeah.
No one wants any pizza?
All right, well, uh, let's get started.
Thank you for coming to the first
What's the point, Mr. Shue?
Coach Sylvester's one of the judges.
She's gonna crush us.
Artie, you don't know that.
Yes, we do.
She told us at Cheerios practice.
Yeah, she said,
"I'm going to crush Glee Club."
PUCK: A whole freaking year.
All that hard work for nothing.
I'm sorry.
I just really love you guys.
You know how many Facebook friends I had
Two. My parents.
Rachel was right.
Being a part of something special--
I just can't
Wait. Who says it's going to be over?
Please. You think Puck and Santana
She has a point.
Mr. Schuester?
Do you think instead of nominating songs,
Glee Club this year?
WILL: It took everything I had not to cry.
It's like they've all walked a thousand miles
What exactly are you looking for from me here?
Some guidance.
Do you remember when you were going
Do you remember why?
Because I loved what I was doing.
And isn't that what you've been drilling
That that feeling is way more important
I miss you.
I'm seeing someone.
What?
His-his name's Carl.
Carl... Howell.
He's my dentist.
He's always been very impressed with my oral hygiene,
We've been going out every night since then.
You two haven't...?
Sorry. I'm-I'm sorry.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. No, no, no, that's... No.
It's fine. That's fine.
I just feel like you and
I had our shot, Will.
Thanks for the help.
Um, no, by the way.
We haven't.
♪  Up and down the boulevard ♪
♪  Their shadows ♪
♪  Searching in the night ♪
♪  Streetlights, people ♪
♪  Living just to find emotion ♪
♪  Hiding somewhere ♪
♪  In the night. ♪
Hey! We need to talk.
We had a chance of keeping it together
You're our leader, Rachel.
The way you're on everyone all the time is annoying, but
You and I are going to fix this.
We're going to Regionals, and we're going to win this thing.
RACHEL: Mr. Schuester, Finn and I
Me first. Have a seat.
Nine months ago, there were five of you in here.
And we sucked.
I mean, we really sucked.
Bad.
One day, all of you are going to be gone.
And all of this, all of us
It will take you a second to remember everyone's name.
Someone will have to remind you
Life only
And I love you guys too much
Now, I was going to quit once,
Don't Stop Believing."
It was a nine,
We're doing "Don't Stop" at Regionals?
And then some.
We are doing a Journey medley.
Because who cares what happens when we get there
Rachel?
You had something you wanted to say?
Just that we're all really glad you didn't become an accountant.
Regionals,
And now, our panel of judges.
He's an international musical sensation,
She's a four-time Grammy winner
Olivia Newton-John!
He's a two-time local
Emmy winner and broadcasting icon,
WOHN news anchor Rod Remington!
She is fresh off her fifth consecutive
National Cheerleading Title
I'm A Winner and You're Fat,
Ohio's home-grown iconoclast,
Coach Sue Sylvester!
And now, our first performance of the evening,
Aural Intensity!
: *  You raise me up... *
♪  You have to believe we are magic... ♪
A mash up of Olivia Newto n-John and Josh Groban.
Are you kidding me?!
Somebody tipped them off about the judges. Guys, we can't
We just got to keep our heads in the game and focus.
Even though we know we can't win?
Yes.
If this is only about winning for you guys,
And we should just all go home,
Besides,
ARTIE: What?
Finn's dancing.
Right? Come on.
Now let's get out there. We got two minutes.
Aural Intensity's almost finished.
Bring it in. Come on. Come on.
Let's go, go, go, go, go and...
ALL: Whoa!
Break a leg.
I love you.
ANNOUNCER: Ladies and Gentleman, our second competitors,
McKinley High's New Directions!
♪  Highway run ♪
♪  Into the midnight sun ♪
♪  Wheels go round and round ♪
♪  You're on my mind ♪
♪  Restless hearts ♪
♪  Sleep alone tonight ♪
♪  Sending all my love ♪
♪  Along the wire ♪
BOTH: *  They say that the road ain't no place to start a family *
♪  Right down the line it's been you and me ♪
♪  And loving a music man ain't always ♪
♪  What it'supposed to be ♪
RACHEL: *  Oh, boy *
♪  You stand by me ♪
BOTH: *  I'm forever yours *
♪  Faithfully ♪
*  Oh, oh, oh, oh *
*  I'm still yours... * *  Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
♪  I'm still yours... ♪
*  Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh *
*  Oh, oh, oh, oh *
♪  I'm still yours... ♪
♪  Faithfully. ♪
♪  Any way you want it, that's the way you need it ♪
♪  Any way you want it ♪
♪  Oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh ♪
FINN: *  She loves to laugh *
♪  She loves to sing ♪
*  Ba da * *  She does everything *
*  Ba da * *  She loves to move *
*  Ba da, ba da * *  She loves to groove *
FINN AND RACHEL:
*  She loves the lovin' things *
♪  It won't be long, yeah ♪
♪  Till you're alone ♪
*  When you lover * *  Lover *
*  Oh, he hasn't come home * *  Ooh, oh-oh-oh *
♪  'Cause he's lovin' ♪
*  Lovin' * *  He's touchin' *
*  Touchin' *
♪  He's squeezin' ♪
♪  Another ♪
*  Another... *
♪  Any way you want, that's the way you need it ♪
♪  Any way you want it ♪
*  Any way you want it *
♪  She said, "Any way you want it" ♪
♪  "That's the way you need it" ♪
♪  "Any way you want it" ♪
*  Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh *
*  I was alone * *  Ba da *
*  I never knew * *  Ba da *
♪  What good love could do ♪
*  Ba da *
FINN AND RACHEL: *  Ooh, then we touched *
*  Then we sang * *  Ba da *
♪  About the lovin' things ♪
*  'Cause he's lovin' * *  Lovin' *
*  He's touchin' * *  Touchin' *
♪  He's squeezin' ♪
*  Another * *  Yeah, yeah... *
♪  Any way you want it, that's the way you need it ♪
*  Any way you want it * *
Any way you want it *
♪  She said, "Any way you want it, that's the way you need" ♪
♪  "Any way you want it" ♪
♪  Oh, oh-oh, oh-oh, oh-oh ♪
♪  Na, na-na, na, na-na ♪
♪  Na, na-na, na, na ♪
♪  Na, na-na, na-na ♪
♪  Any you want it, that's the way you need it. ♪
*  Da, da, da, da *
*  Da, da, da, da... *
♪  Just a small town girl ♪
*  Da, da, da... *
♪  Living in a lonely world ♪
*  Da, da, da, da... *
♪  She took the midnight train going anywhere ♪
♪  Just a city boy ♪
♪  Born and raised in South Detroit ♪
*  Da, da, da, da... *
♪  He took the midnight train going anywhere ♪
♪  Da, da ♪
♪  A singer in a smoky room ♪
♪  A smell of wine and cheap perfume ♪
♪  For a smile they can share the night ♪
♪  It goes on and on and on and on ♪
*  Strangers, waiting * *  Da, da, da, da *
*  Da, da *
♪  Up and down the boulevard ♪
♪  Their shadows searching in the night ♪
*  Da, da *
♪  Streetlight, people ♪
♪  Living just to find emotion ♪
♪  Hiding somewhere ♪
♪  In the night ♪
♪  Don't stop... ♪
♪  Don't stop believin' ♪
♪  Hold on to that feeling ♪
♪  Streetlight, people ♪
♪  Whoa... ♪
♪  Don't stop. ♪
That was awesome!
Oh, my God!
We've got second place in the bag.
Screw that. We are going to win this!
Quinney?
Mom.
What are you doing here?
Is Dad okay...?
I came to hear you sing.
You were wonderful.
I'm-I'm so sorry I missed
Were there a lot?
I left your father.
Well, I-I... kicked m out, actually.
He was having an affair
Quinney,
I want you to come home with me.
I can turn the guest room into a nursery.
Oh, sweetie, say something.
My water just broke.
? is This real? ? *  Is this just fantasy? *
♪  Caught in a landslide ♪
♪  No escape from reality ♪
♪  Open your eyes ♪
♪  Look up to the skies and see ♪
*  I'm just a poor boy * *  Ooh *
*  Ah * *  I need no sympathy *
*  Because I'm easy come, easy go *
*  Little high, little low *
♪  Any way the wind blows doesn't really matter ♪
*  To me *
♪  To me ♪
♪  Mama ♪
♪  Just killed a man ♪
♪  Put a gun against his head ♪
♪  Pulled my trigger ♪
♪  Now he's dead ♪
♪  Mama ♪ Mom, it hurts so bad!
♪  Life had justegun...
♪ My daughter is having a baby.
♪  But now I've gone ♪ Uh, right this way.
♪  And thrown it all away ♪
Wait! Wait!
I want Mercedes with me, too.
♪  Mama ♪
♪  Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh ♪
♪  Didn't mean to make you cry ♪
♪  If I'm not back again this time tomorrow ♪
♪  Carry on, carry on ♪
♪  As if nothing really matters ♪
♪  Too late ♪
♪  My time has come ♪
♪  Sends shivers down my spine ♪
♪  Body's aching all the time ♪
♪  Good-bye everybody ♪
♪  I've got to go ♪
♪  Got to leave you all behind and face the truth ♪
Mommy! *  Mama *
*  Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh * QUINN: Ooh!
*  Any way the wind blows *
♪  I don't want to die ♪
♪  I sometimes wish I'd never been born at all... ♪
It's never coming, ever!
Shut up!
Ooh, you suck! You suck! You suck! You suck!
Come on, Quinney.
♪  I see a little silhouetto of a man ♪
♪  Scaramouche, scaramouche, will you do the fandango? ♪
♪  Thunderbolt and lightning ♪
♪  Very very frightening me ♪
*  Galileo * *  Galileo *
♪  Galileo figaro ♪
*  Magnifico *
♪  I'm just a poor boy, nobody loves me ♪
*  He's just a poor boy from a poor family
*
*  Spare him his life from this monstrosity
♪  Easy come, easy go, will you let me go? ♪
*  Bismillah! *
*  No! We will not let you go *
Let me go! *  Let him go *
*  Bismillah! We will not let you go! *
Let me go! *  Let him go! *
♪  Bismillah! ♪
*  We will not let you go *
Let me go!
*  Will not let you go, let me go *
*  Will not let you go, let him go *
*  Oh, oh, oh *
No! No! No! No! No! No! *  No! No! No! No!
No! No! *
Okay, she's crowning! *  Oh, mama mia, mama mia *
♪  Mama mia, let me go ♪ Push, baby.
♪  Beelzebub has a devil put aside ♪
Come on, Quinn, push. *  For me *
♪  For me ♪
♪  For me! ♪
♪  So you think you can stone me and spit in my eye ♪
♪  So you think you can love me and leave me to die ♪
♪  Oh, baby ♪
♪  Can't do this to me, baby ♪
♪  Just gotta get out, just gotta get right out of here ♪
♪  Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪  Ooh, yeah, ooh, yeah ♪
♪  Nothing really matters ♪
♪  Anyone can see ♪
♪  To me ♪
♪  Any way the wind blows. ♪
Hi. Hi.
Congratulations.
Thanks, Rachel.
But we beat you today.
Jessie's a good singer, but
Vocal Adrenaline's best days are behind it.
So I have a proposition for you.
Come teach at McKinley.
Excuse me?
You and-and Mr. Schuester could be co-directors.
We'd be unstoppable.
There's so much that you can teach me.
So much only you can teach me.
Oh, Rachel, I can't do this anymore.
I'm tired of coaching glee club.
I want a life.
It took meeting you to realize
I need some balance, you know?
I need a house and a garden
I missed out on my chance with you,
And I can't let that happen again.
Where's the rest of your team?
They're, uh... they're at the hospital.
Quinn had her baby. Is she okay?
Yeah, she's fine.
It was, um...
It's a beautiful baby girl.
Newton-John? You're dead to me.
Remington, Horsey, have a seat and listen up.
I don't care who comes in first,
I don't care who places send, but I have
Sue, if I may.
That "Bohemian Rhapsody"
You know, I partied with Freddy
Mercury back in the '70s,
Back then, people weren't so obsessed with labels.
I, for one, was offended
I think Aural Intensity should win.
Yes.
Two questions. One: Are you single?
And two: How about those New Directions?
I liked them. I thought they had a lot of... heart.
Heart? Oh, please.
Talk about blatant tokenism.
That whole "We're inspiring, we're a ragtag
I couldn't agree more. Let's vote.
The production values simply weren't there.
Couldn't they afford better costumes?
Are they a poor person school?
GROBAN: I thought that brunette had an amazing voice.
Brunettes have no place
Oh, come on. They're just kids.
That's no excuse. By the time I was 14,
I'd already formed a band.
When Josh Groban was their age,
As the only educator here, let me point out
Is that what you tell yourself to get to sleep at night?
Some people just simply don't have talent.
You think you're a celebrity. You're not.
You just try hard. That's about it.
Olivia Newton-John has a valid point here.
You have a lot in common
Underachievers with delusions of grandeur.
Dagnabbit!
Now even I have to admit,
I'm a little confused
Wasn't the theme tonight supposed to be celebrity judges?
Kiss my ass, Josh Groban!
I am a internationall y-ranked cheerleading coach!
Who lives in Ohio. When this is done
You'll be staying here.
Just like those kids.
I think we've all made up our minds.
Let's vote.
Thank you all for coming.
As you all know, glee club
And I honestly can't even finish that sentence.
So let's just get to it.
The 2010 Midwest Regional Runners-up
Aural Intensity!
SUE: Very good.
Mm-hmm.
And now,
Show Choir Champions
Vocal Adrenaline!
We didn't even place.
Love. She looks like you.
Do you want to keep her?
No.
Do you?
Did you love me?
Yes.
Especially now.
Which one is yours?
What are you doing here?
I see her now.
She looks like you.
Does she have a name?
No.
Beth.
Pretty.
I like that name.
How do you even call yourself a principal?
Okay, this is... this is it. This is not...
Emma?
Emma?! What was that about? It's so unfair.
Will, your kids have worked so hard for this.
Did you know he's already given your choir room to the Mock UN?
A deal's a deal. We lost, Emma.
Because Sue cheated!
She cheated, Will, and where do you think
We can't let her win this one!
How can you just stand there and be so calm about this?
How can you just give up so easily?
I've tried, Emma,
It-It's over.
No. No, it's never over.
I don't care what anybody says.
Some things are worth fighting for.
You mean like the kids? Yes, of course.
Anything else? No.
No. This is about the glee club.
This is not about us.
The hell it is.
I love you, Emma.
There, I finally said it.
And you love me, and dentist or no,
RACHEL: Mr. Schuester?
Yeah.
Can you please come to the auditorium?
Sure.
So we have something we need to say to you.
In the beginning of this year,
I was just another football player.
I had a stutter.
I was a closeted diva.
I used to be captain of the Cheerios.
I was afraid to dance outside my room.
I hated everyone in this club.
So did I.
I wasn't honest about who I was.
I was tossing kids into Dumpsters.
I had never kissed a girl before.
And I was getting slushied.
I didn't-I didn't have a father.
Someone I could look up to.
Model myself after.
Someone who could show me what it really meant to be a man.
We don't care what the judges say.
We won.
Because we had you as a teacher.
MERCEDES: And Glee Club will never end,
Mr. Shue, because...
And you're in all of us now.
♪  Those schoolgirl days ♪
♪  Of telling tales ♪
♪  And biting nails are gone ♪
♪  But in my mind ♪
♪  I know they will ♪
♪  Still live on and on ♪
♪  But how do you thank someone ♪
♪  Who has taken you from crayons to perfume? ♪
♪  Oh, it isn't easy ♪
♪  But I'll try ♪
♪  If you wanted the sky,
I would write across the sky ♪
♪  In letters that would soar ♪
♪  A thousand feet high ♪
♪  To Sir, with love ♪
♪  The time has come ♪
♪  For closing books ♪
♪  And long last looks must end ♪
♪  And as I leave ♪
♪  I know that I am leaving ♪
♪  My best friend ♪
♪  A friend who taught me right from wrong ♪
♪  And weak from strong, that's a lot to learn ♪
♪  What can I give you in return? ♪
♪  Oh, if you wanted the moon ♪
♪  I would try to make a start ♪
♪  But I would rather ♪
♪  You let me give my heart ♪
♪  To Sir, with love. ♪
It's as barren as me in here, Will.
Moving on to greener pastures?
Did you just come to gloat, Sue?
Mostly.
Well... congratulations.
You got what you wanted.
I should shake your hand.
Not unless you got some hand sanitizer.
I've seen that car you drive;
I don't want to catch poor.
Explain something to me.
Maybe we weren't good enough yet to beat Vocal Adrenaline-- fine.
But we were so much better than Aural Intensity.
Oh, William, I can't reveal how the voting went down.
That would betray my sacred oath as judge or something.
The results simply show
All I can say is casting my vote was easy.
It reflected exactly how
I felt in my heart
Well, Sue, congratulations.
You win.
I lose.
The kids lose.
I know you think I'm heartless, Will,
I spend large segments of each day
And I recently contacted
And I know that you think I'm a bad person
And I've proven that I can wipe you and your Glee Club
But what kind of a world would that be, Will?
A world where I couldn't constantly ridicule your hair.
World where I couldn't make fun of you for tearing up
And you know what, Will?
Sue Sylvester's not sure
So I had a little talk with Figgins.
Glee Club gets another year.
I get what I want.
Do you really not understand
Enough, Sue!
I will not be blackmailed by you anymore!
I will tell my wife of our heated sexual congress
One last chit, Figgy.
Give the glee club another year, and I won't mention us
Huh?
We have another year?
You're a good teacher, Will.
Now, I don't like you so much.
But I admire you
I really do.
Bon chance, William.
I relish the thought of another full year
You know, Sue, inside...
You have a heart.
Okay, let go of my hand.
Hey...
I appreciate what you're doing for these kids.
I won't forget it.
And I'm seriously going to puke in your mouth.
We've got another year.
What?
Come on, we got another year!
What?! Oh, my God!
Yeah!
Are you serious?!
: Whoa!
Okay, you guys, I think this is the perfect opportunity for us
Guys, you've all worked really hard this year,
Take the summer off.
Have some fun.
Oh, but before you go,
I have something for you.
You all sang for me the other day,
Puck, if you're ready.
♪  Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪  Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪  Somewhere ♪
♪  Over the rainbow ♪
♪  Way up high ♪
♪  There's a land that I dreamed of ♪
♪  Once in a lullaby... ♪
♪  Oh, somewhere ♪
♪  Over the rainbow ♪
♪  Skies are blue ♪
♪  And the dreams that you dare to dream ♪
♪  Really do come true... ♪
All the adoption papers seem to be in order.
But there's no name on the birth certificate yet.
It's Beth.
♪  Oh, someday I'll wish upon a star ♪
♪  And wake up where the clouds are far ♪
♪  Behind me ♪
♪  Where troubles melt like lemon drops ♪
♪  High above the chimney tops ♪
♪  That's where ♪
♪  You'll find me ♪
♪  Oh, somewhere ♪
♪  Over the rainbow ♪
♪  Bluebirds fly ♪
♪  Birds fly over the rainbow ♪
♪  Why then, oh, why can't I? ♪
♪  I... ♪
Synced By YesCool WwW.MY-SUBS.com